

Prague, Czech Republic



lukas.bunat@gmail.com



+420 731 277 533



bunat.cz 💸



bunatl



lukasbunat





### Full-Stack & Software Developer

I am an enthusiastic developer with a passion for programming and technology. I have been in IT and specifically in software development for 4+ years. Right now, I am looking for an opportunity that will utilize and further expand my skillset. My focus is to build platforms that will help grow and scale any business needs.

I don't just code, thanks to my strong educational background, I have a wide range of skills like planning, theoretical informatics or analytical & theoretical thinking that helps me in finding clever solutions. I have had studied at many different universities all over the world and I take great pride in my international education. I thrive on multicultural teams and enjoy resolving everyday challenges. I am always open to new opportunities and eager and open to learn more!



## **Technical Skills**

Software development

Full-Stack technologies Front EndReact.js 16.12, JavaScript ES6/2017, TypeScript, HTML5, CSS3, SASSBack EndNode.js, express.js, JAVA EE, "REST APIs", apache2, nginxDatabaseSQL (MySQL, MS SQL Server), No-SQL (MongoDB - Mongoose, Monk)OtherYarn, npm, webpack, parcel, babel, postman

Software Collaboration Theoretical informatics Computer architecture

Other

Tableau, Rapid Miner, Wolfram Alpha, Modelio, MS Office Suite, AutoCAD, Inventor

GIT, GitLab, JIRA, Trello, Slack, G Suite, MS Teams

C, C++, JAVA SE, bash, AHK

Calculus, Linear Algebra, Algorithms, Speed and memory efficiency

Data and number representation, OS/memory/cache/FS management, multitasking

Business Intelligence, Testing, PC/WWW networking, UML Data analysis, Logical thinking, Critical & analytical thinking



# **Experiences**

### **Work Experiences**

**Freelancer,** "on & off" contracts

09/2019 - Present

Business websites

**○** GitHub

- Web application (MERN)
- Personal full-Stack projects (JS, node.js, reactJS)
- Wordpress

#### **Internal application Specialist** 05/2018–05/2019

O2 Czech Republic a.s., Prague, Czech Republic

- O2TV platform and O2TV set-top box
- Company internal and external software and web application development
- https://www.o2tv.cz/, O2TV
- > Java EE, JS, HTML5, CSS3, C

### **Internships**

Big Data Architect

10/2017-12/2017

Comillas Pontifical University, Madrid, Spain

- Application of Clustering Methods for Discovering Patterns of Energy
- PySpark, Jupyter, Hadoop

#### **Network Engineer**

03/2017-06/2017

Kyungpook National University, Daegu, South Korea

- Network routing and latency simulations on COOJA Simulator
- Wireshark, COOJA

From 2014 to 2019 I had been working as a tutor at international student club at Czech Technical University.



## **Soft Skills**



New creative and innovative approaches to problem solving



Very good (cross-culture) communication for constructive teamwork



Enthusiastic and passionate about learning new things and technologies



Decisiveness and good decision-making (even uder pressure), leadership



Effective time managment to ensure tasks' deadlines are met



# **Education**

University, Year(s) of Study		Field of study, Faculty	Location
STOLA FROM	University of Economics	Information systems and technologies	Prague,
PRAZE	2019 - Present	Faculty of informatics and statistics	V Czech Republic
<b>15.08</b>	Czech Technical University	Open Informatics	Prague,
	2019	Faculty of Electrical Engineering	▼ Czech Republic
<b>ISIS</b>	University of Finance and Administration	Applied Informatics, <b>Graduate, Bc.</b>	Prague, Czech Republic
	2018-2019	Faculty of Economics	
	Czech Technical University	Information Systems and Management	Prague, Czech Republic
	2014–2018	Faculty of Information Technology	
THE STATE OF THE S	Kyungpook National University	Exchange studies	P Daegu, South Korea
	2017	College of IT Engineering	
STEOF HOUSE	Indian Institute of Technology Madras	Exchange studies	Chennai,
Ell. Manlan and Sch	2016	Department of Computer Science	<b>▼</b> India
TO COCKING TO THE PARTY OF THE	Delft University of Technology	Case study of Earthquakes in Netherland	P Delft, Netherlands
	2016	The ATHENS Programme	
	Mayflower College of English	Summer language school	Plymouth,
	2012		United Kingdom



# **Certificates**



CISCO Academy

CCNA 1 (2013)



Autodesk AutoCAD (2014) Inventor (2014)



**KFN of UNESCO** 

Cross Culture Awereness Programme